Bright and blinding, haa..
Dancing to the sun's rhythm, we dance and sing "Ole"
Different rhythmic stomps join together in unison
Everyone's got things they love and things they don't
No two people in the world are exactly alike, turning like the colors in a kaleidoscope
Now come here
and feel, feel, feel the energy
Just make a move
Give into the impulse and clap, clap, clap your hands
one, two, three
Step, step, step let it resonate
Our miracle is just beginning
Dreams and aspirations are one in the same
giving birth to a neww dream
Dance to your heart's content, chicas
Our future is right around the corner
Right now no one knows
the sound of a melody yet to be heard
But when we dance together,
we can bring to future to us
Bright and blinding, ah..